redbulletin.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy

**2\. Information we collect**

2.1 We collect two types of “ **Information**.” Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. **Personally Identifiable Information** means any information that itself identifies you or would easily enable someone to contact and/or identify you, such as your name, social security number, email address or phone number. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** refers to all other information about you that you may provide to us or that we may collect from you.

2.2 You may actively give us Information about yourself when you, among other things, use one of our Properties, create an account (“ **Account** ”) with us, subscribe to a newsletter, purchase a game, product or service, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a customer survey, email us, post in a public forum and/or use our chat/message functionality. The Information that you provide may include your name, gender, date of birth, email address, telephone number, delivery address, billing address and payment information, and login and password. Note also that Information you disclose in public chat and similar forums is accessible by anyone, including third parties not bound by this Policy.

2.3 When you visit one of our Properties, we may also automatically collect, among other things, the following Information even if you have not actively given it to us: your IP address, log-in information, location information (for example, via GPS or WiFi), browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, information about your visit including the URL clickstream to, through and from one of our Properties, products and/or content you viewed or searched for, download errors, length of visits to certain pages and page interaction, and in the case of our mobile applications, the other applications you have downloaded and how you use those applications. We collect Information automatically through the use of various technologies, including through “cookies”, which is explained further below in Section 8.

2.4 We acquire Information from other trusted sources (including, for example, business partners, advertising networks, search information providers, credit reference agencies and social media), and from other Red Bull Media House entities and affiliates, to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically. Note that this includes Information from your social media account when you grant us access to your social media account in connection with, for example, creating an Account with us. Where permitted by law, we may combine this information we receive from other sources, and with information you give to us or that we collect about you.

2.5 If you have created an Account on one of our Properties, you may be able to obtain a copy of the Personally Identifiable Information we collect from you via your Account and correct, amend, or delete Personally Identifiable Information that is inaccurate. You may also close your Account altogether. Before we are able to respond to your request, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide further details about your request. We will endeavour to respond within an appropriate timeframe and, in any event, within any timeframes required by law.

2.6 It is your responsibility to ensure that you submit true, accurate and complete Information via your Account and keep it up to date. You may also update your Personally Identifiable Information by contacting us through the contact details provided below. Please make sure to include your name, username, and post code in your initial correspondence; this helps us protect the details and preferences on your Account from unauthorized access.

2.7 If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any of our Properties, California law permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send us a detailed description of the specific content or information by clicking [here](http://energydrink-us.redbull.com/privacy-contact-form). Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

2.8 In addition, if you are a California resident California law also permits you to request the Personal Information we collect and third parties that received the Personal Information for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To make such a request, please send us a detailed description of the specific content or information by clicking here.
